Guide to the Time Inc. Video Group Records 1934-1989 MS 3009-RG 41
New-York Historical Society
- Series VIII. Time-Life Video Records, 1971-1987; 9.1 Linear feet in 11 records cartons and 1 flat box
  - Subseries VIII.A. Vice President of Co-Productions Haidee Granger Files, 1973-1984; 4 Linear feet in 6 records cartons and 1 flat box
    - Borgias: Cue Sheets, 1982 (Offsite-box 3392, Folder 11)
    - Borgias: Master File, 1978-1983 (Offsite-box 3392, Folder 12)
    - Borgias: Master File [RESTRICTED], 1978-1983 (Offsite-box R59)
    - Borgias: Photographs, undated (Offsite-box 3392, Folder 13)
    - Borgias: Photographs II and News Clippings, undated (Offsite-box 3392, Folder 14-15)
    - Borgias: Press and Publicity, 1980-1981 (Offsite-box 3382, Folder 16)
    - Borgias: Production, 1978-1980 (Offsite-box 3392, Folder 17)
    - Borgias: Treatment, 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 3392, Folder 18)
    - Caught on a Train: Treatment and Correspondence, 1979-1983 (Offsite-box 3392, Folder 19-20)
    - Connections: WQED Contracts [RESTRICTED], 1977-1980 (Offsite-box R59)
    - Granger, Haidee: To Be Expensed or Reimbursed, 1983 (Offsite-box 3392, Folder 21)
    - Headlines: Correspondence, 1982 (Offsite-box 3382, Folder 22)
    - The Long Search [RESTRICTED], 1974-1976 (Offsite-box R59)
    - The Long Search: Xerox Corporation Agreement, 1976-1978 (Offsite-box 3392, Folder 23)
    - The Long Search: Xerox Corporation Agreement [RESTRICTED], 1974-1975 (Offsite-box R59)
    - Magic of Dance: Contracts: BBC/Program License Agreement [RESTRICTED], 1978-1979 (Offsite-box R59)
    - Magic of Dance: Correspondence, 1980-1983 (Offsite-box 3392, Folder 24)
    - Magic of Dance: Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1979-1982 (Offsite-box R59)
    - Making of Mankind: Contracts [RESTRICTED], 1980-1983 (Offsite-box R59)
    - Making of Mankind: Correspondence, 1978-1983 (Offsite-box 3392, Folder 25)
    - Making of Mankind: Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1982-1983 (Offsite-box R59)
    - Making of Mankind: Delivery of Materials and Music Cue Sheets, 1981 (Offsite-box 3393, Folder 1)
    - Making of Mankind: Press Articles, 1979-1981 (Offsite-box 3393, Folder 2-3)
    - Making of Mankind: Press Materials, 1976-1981 (Offsite-box 3393, Folder 4-5)
    - Making of Mankind: Publicity, 1977-1981 (Offsite-box 3393, Folder 6)
    - Making of Mankind: Underwriters, 1982 (Offsite-box 3393, Folder 7-8)
    - Mobil Oil, Inc.: Schmertz, Herb [RESTRICTED], 1981-1984 (Offsite-box R59)
    - Nancy Astor: Cast Photos and Resumes, 1981 (Offsite-box 3393, Folder 9-10)
    - Nancy Astor: Master File, 1981-1984 (Offsite-box 3393, Folder 11-12)
    - Nancy Astor: Master File [RESTRICTED], 1981-1983 (Offsite-box R59)
    - Nancy Astor: Music Cue Sheets [EMPTY], undated (Offsite-box 3392, Folder 13)
    - Nancy Astor: Production Schedule, 1981 (Offsite-box 3393, Folder 14)
    - Nancy Astor: Treatment and Script Breakdown, 1979-1981 (Offsite-box 3393, Folder 15)
    - NOVA: "Animal Olympians": Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1982 (Offsite-box R59)
    - NOVA: "It's About Time": WGBH Boston [RESTRICTED], 1982 (Offsite-box R59)
    - Planet Earth: Living Planet: BBC, 1982-1984 (Offsite-box 3393, Folder 16)
    - Planet Earth: The Living Planet: BBC [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Offsite-box R59)
    - Planet Earth: Master File, 1979-1983 (Offsite-box 3393, Folder 17)
    - Planet Earth: Master File [RESTRICTED], 1981 (Offsite-box R59)
    - Planet Earth: Scripts, 1980-1981 (Offsite-box 3393, Folder 18-20)
    - Search for Alexander the Great: Contracts: Artists, Various [RESTRICTED], 1980-1981 (Offsite-box R59)
    - Search for Alexander the Great: Contract: Lefferts, George [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Offsite-box R59)
    - Search for Alexander the Great: Contract: Master Agreement: Time-Life Films/Greeks [RESTRICTED], 1978-1983 (Offsite-box R59)
    - Search for Alexander the Great: Contracts: Raven, Simon [RESTRICTED], 1980 (Offsite-box R59)
    - Search for Alexander the Great: Contract: Sharples, Robert [RESTRICTED], 1981 (Offsite-box R59)
    - Search for Alexander the Great: Copyright Registration [RESTRICTED], 1981 (Offsite-box R59)
    - Search for Alexander the Great: Correspondence, 1978-1982 (Offsite-box 3393, Folder 21-22)
    - Search for Alexander the Great: Correspondence, 1982-1984 (Offsite-box 3394, Folder 1-2)
    - Search for Alexander the Great: Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1980-1983 (Offsite-box R59)
    - Search for Alexander the Great: Distribution, 1981-1984 (Offsite-box 3394, Folder 3)
    - Search for Alexander the Great: Distribution [RESTRICTED], 1982 (Offsite-box R59)
    - Search for Alexander the Great: Financial Register, undated (Offsite-box 3325)
    - Search for Alexander the Great: Greek Revisions, 1981 (Offsite-box 3394, Folder 4)
    - Search for Alexander the Great: Master Agreement, Time-Life Films/Greeks, 1976-1982 (Offsite-box 3394, Folder 5)
    - Search for Alexander the Great: Originals, 1978 (Offsite-box 3394, Folder 6)
    - Search for Alexander the Great: Pre-Production Binder [RESTRICTED], 1978-1980 (Offsite-box R59)
    - Search for Alexander the Great: Pre-Production Binder [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Offsite-box R60)
    - Search for Alexander the Great: Presentation: Originals [RESTRICTED], undated (Offsite-box R60)
    - Search for Alexander the Great: Production Binder 23-03, 1980-1981 (Offsite-box 3394, Folder 7)
    - Search for Alexander the Great: Scripts, undated (Offsite-box 3394, Folder 8-9)
    - Shakespeare: Correspondence, 1977-1984 (Offsite-box 3394, Folder 10-11)
    - Shakespeare: Music Cue Sheets, 1981-1983 (Offsite-box 3394, Folder 12)
    - Shakespeare: Press and Reviews, 1978-1983 (Offsite-box 3394, Folder 13-16)
    - Shakespeare: Schedule and Casting Information, 1979-1981 (Offsite-box 3394, Folder 17)
    - Shock of the New: Chronicle [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Offsite-box R60)
    - Shock of the New: Contracts: BBC: SCETV Program License Agreement [RESTRICTED], 1978-1980 (Offsite-box R60)
    - Shock of the New: Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Offsite-box 3394, Folder 18)
    - Shock of the New: Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1981 (Offsite-box R60)
    - Shock of the New: Hughes, Robert, 1980-1982 (Offsite-box 3394, Folder 19)
    - Shock of the New: Music Cue Sheets, 1980-1984 (Offsite-box 3394, Folder 20)
    - To Serve Them All My Days: Correspondence, 1980-1983 (Offsite-box 3394, Folder 21)
    - To Serve Them All My Days: Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1981-1983 (Offsite-box R60)
    - We the Accused: Correspondence, 1980-1983 (Offsite-box 3394, Folder 22)
    - We the Accused: Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1981 (Offsite-box R60)
    - WGBH: Mobil Mystery Theater, 1975-1983 (Offsite-box 3394, Folder 23)
    - WGBH: Mobil Mystery Theater [RESTRICTED], 1978-1981 (Offsite-box R60)
    - WGBH: Mystery!, 1979-1983 (Offsite-box 3394, Folder 24)
    - WGBH: Mystery! [RESTRICTED], 1978-1980 (Offsite-box R60)
    - WGBH: World About Us, 1973-1979 (Offsite-box 3394, Folder 25)
    - WGBH: World About Us [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Offsite-box R60)
    - Wilderness: "Mato Grosso": Correspondence, 1983 (Offsite-box 3394, Folder 26)
    - Wild, Wild World of Animals: Available Territories, 1981 (Offsite-box 3394, Folder 27)
    - WNET: Correspondence, 1978-1980 (Offsite-box 3394, Folder 28)
    - Shakespeare Plays: Contracts: WNET/BBC, 1977-1983 (Offsite-box R60)
  - Subseries VIII.B. Business Manager Kathy Coraggio Files, 1971-1987; 3 Linear feet in 4 records cartons
    Kathy Coraggio, also known as Katrina Coraggio, first appears on department head lists in July 1982 as the manager of accounting for the Video Group and remains in that position through 1984. In 1985, Coraggio becomes the business manager for Time-Life Video and remains in this position through 1986. In 1987, she is no longer on department head lists.
    The Kathy Coraggio Files cover the period of 1971 to 1987 and focus on her work as the business manager of Time-Life Video. While there are documents from her time as the manager of accounting for the Video Group, the majority of documents do not focus on that work. Additionally, there are some materials that originate from Time-Life Films, these documents are present since Time-Life Video took over many of Time-Life Film's responsibilities when it was phased out. Included in this subseries are agreements, notes, distribution forms, contract overview forms, co-production forms, license agreements overviews, clearance history sheets, re-run analysis, list of air dates, financial analysis, lists of shows and revenue, list of payments, rights evaluations, distribution reports, sales history reports, notes, invoices, check requisition forms, list of contracts, bookkeeping journal entries, financial reports, list of receipts, contract abstracts, profit and loss worksheets, profit participation formula sheets, and correspondence. The correspondence discusses cable sales candidates, agreements, delivery schedule, and costs.
    - According to the Rules, 1972-1974, 1980-1986 (Offsite-box 3397, Folder 1)
    - According to the Rules [RESTRICTED], 1974 (Offsite-box R60)
    - All Creatures Great and Small, 1978-1984 (Offsite-box 3397, Folder 2-3)
    - All Creatures Great and Small: Accounts Receivable, 1981-1984 (Offsite-box 3397, Folder 4)
    - All Creatures Great and Small: Contracts [RESTRICTED], 1981 (Offsite-box R60)
    - All Creatures Great and Small: Correspondence, 1978-1986 (Offsite-box 3397, Folder 5)
    - All Creatures Great and Small: Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Offsite-box R60)
    - All Creatures Great and Small: Royalty Payments, 1983-1987 (Offsite-box 3397, Folder 6)
    - All Creatures Great and Small: Royalty Reports, 1983-1987 (Offsite-box 3397, Folder 7)
    - All's Well That Ends Well, 1981-1986 (Offsite-box 3397, Folder 8)
    - All the World's A Stage, 1980-1984 (Offsite-box 3397, Folder 9)
    - All the World's A Stage [RESTRICTED], 1980 (Offsite-box R60)
    - All the World's A Stage: P and L Analysis, 1980-1984 (Offsite-box 3397, Folder 10)
    - All the World's A Stage: P and L Analysis [RESTRICTED], 1980-1984 (Offsite-box R60)
    - The Ambassador's [RESTRICTED], 1977, 1984 (Offsite-box R60)
    - America, 1971-1975, 1982-1986 (Offsite-box 3397, Folder 11)
    - America [RESTRICTED], 1971, 1985 (Offsite-box R60)
    - The Americans, 1976-1978 (Offsite-box 3397, Folder 12)
    - The Americans [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Offsite-box R60)
    - Anna Karenina, 1975-1977, 1982-1983 (Offsite-box 3397, Folder 13)
    - Anna Karenina [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Offsite-box R60)
    - Anthony and Cleopatra, 1983-1986 (Offsite-box 3397, Folder 14)
    - As You Like It, 1978-1986 (Offsite-box 3397, Folder 15)
    - Ascent of Man, 1973-1976, 1980-1985 (Offsite-box 3397, Folder 16)
    - Ascent of Man [RESTRICTED], 1971 (Offsite-box R60)
    - Borgias, 1981-1985 (Offsite-box 3397, Folder 17)
    - Borgias [RESTRICTED], undated (Offsite-box R60)
    - The Bronx is Burning [RESTRICTED], 1972-1974, 1983, undated (Offsite-box R60)
    - Candide [RESTRICTED], 1973-1974, 1986 (Offsite-box R60)
    - Caught on a Train [RESTRICTED], 1980, 1986 (Offsite-box R60)
    - China, 1983 (Offsite-box 3397, Folder 18)
    - Comedy of Errors, 1983-1986 (Offsite-box 3397, Folder 19)
    - Commanders, 1973, 1986 (Offsite-box 3397, Folder 20)
    - Commanders [RESTRICTED], 1973 (Offsite-box R60)
    - Connections, 1978, 1985 (Offsite-box 3397, Folder 21)
    - Connections [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Offsite-box R60)
    - Coriolanus, 1984-1986 (Offsite-box 3397, Folder 22)
    - Crime and Punishment, 1977-1983 (Offsite-box 3397, Folder 23)
    - Crime and Punishment [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Offsite-box R60)
    - Cymbaline, 1983-1986 (Offsite-box 3397, Folder 24)
    - David Copperfield [RESTRICTED], 1973-1980, 1986 (Offsite-box R60)
    - Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde [RESTRICTED], 1980, 1986, undated (Offsite-box R60)
    - Duchess of Duke Street [RESTRICTED], 1976-1977, 1983, undated (Offsite-box R60)
    - Duchess of Malfi, 1972-1974 (Offsite-box 3397, Folder 25)
    - Duchess of Malfi [RESTRICTED], 1974 (Offsite-box R60)
    - Europe, The Mighty Continent, 1973-1984 (Offsite-box 3397, Folder 26)
    - Europe, the Mighty Continent [RESTRICTED], 1973 (Offsite-box R60)
    - The Explorers, 1973-1975, 1983-1985 (Offsite-box 3397, Folder 27)
    - The Explorer [RESTRICTED], 1975 (Offsite-box R60)
    - Fall of Eagles, 1973-1975, 1983 (Offsite-box 3397, Folder 28)
    - Fall of Eagles [RESTRICTED], 1973 (Offsite-box R60)
    - Fight Against Slavery, 1973-1983 (Offsite-box 3397, Folder 29)
    - Fight Against Slavery [RESTRICTED], 1973 (Offsite-box R60)
    - Gates of Asia [RESTRICTED], 1973-1974, 1983 (Offsite-box R60)
    - Hamlet, 1980, 1986 (Offsite-box 3397, Folder 30)
    - Headlines, 1982 (Offsite-box 3397, Folder 31)
    - Heidi [RESTRICTED], 1974-1986 (Offsite-box R60)
    - Henry IV, 1983-1986 (Offsite-box 3397, Folder 32-33)
    - Henry V, 1979 (Offsite-box 3397, Folder 34)
    - Henry VI, 1979-1986 (Offsite-box 3397, Folder 35-37)
    - Henry VIII, 1979, 1986 (Offsite-box 3397, Folder 38)
    - Horseman Riding By, 1978-1983 (Offsite-box 3397, Folder 39)
    - Horseman Riding By [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Offsite-box R60)
    - Importance of Being Ernest [RESTRICTED], 1973, 1983 (Offsite-box R60)
    - Julius Caesar, 1976, 1986 (Offsite-box 3397, Folder 40)
    - Katherine Mansfield [RESTRICTED], 1973-1974 (Offsite-box R60)
    - Katy, 1976, 1983 (Offsite-box 3397, Folder 41)
    - King Lear, 1982-1986 (Offsite-box 3397, Folder 42)
    - King Oedipus, 1972, 1983 (Offsite-box 3397, Folder 43)
    - Legend of King Arthur, 1979-1986 (Offsite-box 3397, Folder 44)
    - Legend of King Arthur [RESTRICTED], 1980 (Offsite-box R60)
    - Life and Death of King John, 1986 (Offsite-box 3397, Folder 45)
    - Little Lord Fauntleroy [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Offsite-box R60)
    - Living Planet [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Offsite-box R60)
    - Living Planet, 1981-1986 (Offsite-box 3397, Folder 46)
    - Long Search [RESTRICTED], 1975-1983 (Offsite-box R60)
    - Lorna Doone [RESTRICTED], 1976-1980 (Offsite-box R60)
    - The Love Girl and the Innocent [RESTRICTED], 1973-1978 (Offsite-box R60)
    - Love's Labours Lost, 1986 (Offsite-box 3397, Folder 47)
    - Macbeth, 1983-1986 (Offsite-box 3397, Folder 48)
    - Madame Bovary [RESTRICTED], 1975-1977 (Offsite-box R60)
    - Magic of Dance, 1979-1984 (Offsite-box 3397, Folder 49)
    - Magic of Dance [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Offsite-box R60)
    - Making of Mankind [RESTRICTED], 1978-1986 (Offsite-box R60)
    - Making of Natural History [RESTRICTED], 1972-1974 (Offsite-box R60)
    - Malice Aforethought [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Offsite-box R60)
    - Marie Curie [RESTRICTED], 1977-1979 (Offsite-box R60)
    - Master of Ballantrae [RESTRICTED], 1974-1975 (Offsite-box R60)
    - Mayor of Casterbridge [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Offsite-box R60)
    - Measure for Measure [RESTRICTED], 1979, 1986 (Offsite-box R60)
    - Merchant of Venice [RESTRICTED], 1972-1974, 1980, 1986 (Offsite-box R60)
    - Merry Wives of Windsor, 1982-1986 (Offsite-box 3397, Folder 50)
    - Microbes and Men [RESTRICTED], 1973-1974, 1984 (Offsite-box R60)
    - Midsummer Night's Dream, 1981-1986 (Offsite-box 3397, Folder 51)
    - Much Ado About Nothing, 1986 (Offsite-box 3397, Folder 52)
    - Nancy Astor [RESTRICTED], 1981-1984 (Offsite-box R60)
    - Navajo (Horizon Series) [RESTRICTED], 1972-1973, 1985 (Offsite-box R60)
    - Nicholas Nickelby [RESTRICTED], 1976-1977 (Offsite-box R60)
    - Nine Tailors [RESTRICTED], 1974 (Offsite-box R60)
    - Nova, 1982-1985 (Offsite-box 3397, Folder 54)
    - Nova [RESTRICTED], 1981-1986 (Offsite-box R60)
    - Othello, 1983-1986 (Offsite-box 3397, Folder 55)
    - Pallisers, 1974-1983 (Offsite-box 3397, Folder 56)
    - Pallisers [RESTRICTED], 1973 (Offsite-box R60)
    - Peer Gynt, 1972-1974, 1982-1983 (Offsite-box 3397, Folder 57)
    - Peer Gynt [RESTRICTED], 1974 (Offsite-box R60)
    - Pericles, 1986 (Offsite-box 3397, Folder 58)
    - Pinocchio, 1978-1986 (Offsite-box 3397, Folder 59)
    - Pinocchio [RESTRICTED], 1979-1984 (Offsite-box R60)
    - Plain Murder [RESTRICTED], 1978-1983 (Offsite-box R61)
    - The Prince and the Pauper [RESTRICTED], 1975-1980 (Offsite-box R61)
    - Rebecca [RESTRICTED], 1975-1980 (Offsite-box R61)
    - Richard II, 1978, 1986 (Offsite-box 3397, Folder 60)
    - Richard III, 1983-1986 (Offsite-box 3397, Folder 61)
    - Robin Hood [RESTRICTED], 1975-1983 (Offsite-box R61)
    - Romeo and Juliet, 1978, 1986 (Offsite-box 3397, Folder 62)
    - A Room with a View [RESTRICTED], 1973-1974 (Offsite-box R61)
    - The Saboteurs of Telemark [RESTRICTED], 1973-1974 (Offsite-box R61)
    - Search for the Nile, 1971, 1983 (Offsite-box 3397, Folder 63)
    - Search for the Nile [RESTRICTED], 1971 (Offsite-box R61)
    - Shakespeare: BBC, 1980-1985 (Offsite-box 3397, Folder 64-65)
    - Shakespeare: BBC [RESTRICTED], 1977-1985 (Offsite-box R61)
    - Shakespeare: BBC: CBP Reporting [RESTRICTED], 1976-1977, 1983-1985 (Offsite-box R61)
    - Shakespeare: Series, 1978-1986 (Offsite-box 3397, Folder 66-67)
    - Shakespeare: Series [RESTRICTED], 1976-1981 (Offsite-box R61)
    - Shock of the New, 1980-1987 (Offsite-box 3398, Folder 1)
    - Story Behind the Story, 1973, 1983 (Offsite-box 3398, Folder 2)
    - A Tale of Two Cities, 1979-1983 (Offsite-box 3398, Folder 3)
    - Taming of the Shrew, 1980-1986 (Offsite-box 3398, Folder 4)
    - The Tempest, 1980-1986 (Offsite-box 3398, Folder 5)
    - Third Party Profit Sharing, 1975-1981 (Offsite-box 3398, Folder 6-8)
    - Third Party Profit Sharing [RESTRICTED], 1978-1980 (Offsite-box R61)
    - Timon of Athens, 1983-1986 (Offsite-box 3398, Folder 9)
    - Titus Andronicus, 1986 (Offsite-box 3398, Folder 10)
    - Train the Trainer, 1984 (Offsite-box 3398, Folder 11)
    - Troilus and Cressida, 1981-1986 (Offsite-box 3398, Folder 12)
    - Tutankhamun's Egypt [RESTRICTED], 1972-1974, 1983 (Offsite-box R61)
    - Twelfth Night, 1980-1986 (Offsite-box 3398, Folder 13)
    - Two Gentlemen of Verona, 1986 (Offsite-box 3398, Folder 14)
    - Voyage of Charles Darwin [RESTRICTED], 1978-1986 (Offsite-box R61)
    - War and Peace, 1973-1975, 1984-1985 (Offsite-box 3398, Folder 15)
    - War and Peace [RESTRICTED], 1974 (Offsite-box R61)
    - Who Sank the Lusitania [RESTRICTED], 1972-1974, 1983 (Offsite-box R61)
    - Wilderness [RESTRICTED], 1974-1983 (Offsite-box R61)
    - A Winter's Tale, 1981-1986 (Offsite-box 3398, Folder 16)
    - Wodehouse Playhouse, 1975-1983 (Offsite-box 3398, Folder 17)
    - Wodehouse Playhouse [RESTRICTED], 1976-1987 (Offsite-box R61)
    - Word About Us, 1974 (Offsite-box 3398, Folder 18)
    - Wuthering Heights [RESTRICTED], 1978-1983 (Offsite-box R61)
    - Yesterday's Witness [RESTRICTED], 1979-1983 (Offsite-box R61)
  - Subseries VIII.C. BBC Financial Files, 1974-1987; 1.3 Linear feet in 3 records cartons
    The BBC Financial Files cover the period of 1974 to 1987 and focus on the financial relationship between Time-Life Video and the British Broadcast Corporation (BBC). While the majority of documents are from Time-Life Video, there are some documents that were created by Time-Life Film. These documents are present since Time-Life Video took over many of Time-Life Film's responsibilities when it was phased out. Included in this subseries are a list of requests for extension of rights, invoices, list of outstanding invoices, contract abstracts, distribution forms, notes, BBC residual obligations report, payment history sheet, residual calculations report, currency rates sheet, assets and liability analysis, syndication analysis, cash flow stats, revenue status report, and correspondence. The correspondence discusses clearance notices, residuals, payments, licensing, sales, and equity agreements.
    - BBC: Clearance Correspondence, 1975-1979 (Offsite-box 3395, Folder 1)
    - BBC: Clearance Notices, undated (Offsite-box 3395, Folder 2)
    - BBC: Clearance Update Sheet, undated (Offsite-box 3395, Folder 3)
    - BBC: Co-Productions: Investments, 1978-1986 (Offsite-box 3395, Folder 4)
    - BBC: Co-Productions: Residual Payment, 1981-1982 (Offsite-box 3395, Folder 6-8)
    - BBC: Correspondence, 1975, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 3395, Folder 9-10)
    - BBC: Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1986 (Offsite-box R60)
    - BBC: Cross Collateralization Costs, 1974-1985 (Offsite-box 3395, Folder 11-12)
    - BBC: Enterprises [RESTRICTED], 1974-1979 (Offsite-box R60)
    - BBC: Estimates/Budgets, 1982 (Offsite-box 3395, Folder 13)
    - BBC: Fall of Eagles: Book Royalty [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Offsite-box R60)
    - BBC: Latin American Production, 1981-1984 (Offsite-box 3395, Folder 14)
    - BBC: Latin American Residuals, 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 3395, Folder 15)
    - BBC: Living Machines, 1982 (Offsite-box 3395, Folder 16)
    - BBC: Mobil, 1982-1983 (Offsite-box 3395, Folder 17)
    - BBC: Mobil [RESTRICTED], 1982-1983 (Offsite-box R60)
    - BBC: Premium Recoupment, 1974, 1980-1984 (Offsite-box 3395, Folder 18)
    - BBC: Residual Calculations, 1982-1984 (Offsite-box 3395, Folder 19)
    - BBC: Residual Payments, 1982-1984 (Offsite-box 3395, Folder 20)
    - BBC: Residual Schedules, 1984 (Offsite-box 3395, Folder 21)
    - BBC: Royalty Report: Latin America, 1983-1987 (Offsite-box 3395, Folder 22)
    - BBC: Royalty Reporting, 1978-1986 (Offsite-box 3395, Folder 23-24)
    - BBC: Royalty Reporting [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Offsite-box R60)
    - BBC: Royalty Reports: To TLV, 1985-1987 (Offsite-box 3396, Folder 1)
    - Unpaid BBC Bills, 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 3396, Folder 2)
  - Subseries VIII.D. Co-Production Royalty Files, 1981-1986; 0.8 Linear feet in 1 records carton
    The Co-Production Royalty Files cover the period of 1981 to 1986 and contain royalty reports. Within this subseries is two sets of files, the BBC Royalty Reports and the Co-Production Royalty Reports. The BBC reports are for co-productions made in conjunction the British Broadcast Corporation (BBC). The Co-Production reports do not identify the company the co-productions were made with.
    - BBC Royalty Reports, 1981-1982 (Offsite-box 3396, Folder 3-6)
    - Co-Production Royalty Reports, 1983-1986 (Offsite-box 3396, Folder 7-15)
- Series IX. Time-Life Broadcast/Time-Life Broadcast Inc. Records, 1937-1974; 186897; 11.3 Linear feet in 13 records cartons
  While sometimes listed separately within department head lists, Time-Life Broadcast, sometimes referred to as Broadcasting, and Time-Life Broadcast Inc. are indistinguishable and appear to be the same group. It is unclear why one is listed as a group within Time Inc. while the other is listed as a subsidiary.
  Time-Life Broadcasting was originally created in 1961 and was incorporated in 1962. At the time the organization was formed, their main interest was in exploring and research community antenna television systems, also known as CATV. By building this antenna system, they hoped that homes that were too far from broadcasting stations might be able to receive television reception and this wider network would allow them to build a pay-tv system in the future. To make this effort a reality, Time-Life Broadcast purchased Sterling Information Services in 1965.
  Along with purchasing the systems needed to broadcast television, Time-Life Broadcast also bought local television stations, such as WTCN-TV-AM in Minneapolis-St. Paul. Owning television stations allowed Time-Life Broadcast to broaden the scope of their efforts and create their own programming. Not only did they have the means to broadcast television but now they could create, produce, and sell their own product. One notable project that Time-Life Broadcast tried to market was a relaunch of March of Time featuring Henry Cabot Lodge.
  Time-Life Broadcast. Time Inc. Subject Files (MS 3009-RG 1), New-York Historical Society.